{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "37 + 79",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 97",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 61",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 48",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 55",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 66",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 56",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 4",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 60",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 5",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 75",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 77",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 82",
      "answer": 182
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 96",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 69",
      "answer": 163
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 61",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 68",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 18",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 25",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 80",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 68",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 68",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 25",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 34",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 97",
      "answer": 169
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 40",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 70",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 81",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 74",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 8",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 93",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 7",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 1",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 63",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 41",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 43",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 85",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 51",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 95",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 40",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 5",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 58",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 43",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 29",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 36",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 77",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 3",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 98",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 33",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 55",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 64",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 8",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 57",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 91",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 98",
      "answer": 181
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 35",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 38",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 70",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 38",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 41",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 71",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 95",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 25",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 72",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 19",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 6",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 65",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 98",
      "answer": 192
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 96",
      "answer": 183
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 76",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 8",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 54",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 41",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 61",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 49",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 84",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 16",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 7",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 40",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 71",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 44",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 28",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 41",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 93",
      "answer": 191
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 57",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 28",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 77",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 80",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 15",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 26",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 24",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 75",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 42",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 56",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 75",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 26",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 40",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 65",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 50",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 26",
      "answer": 35
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 9,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 800,
      "to": 900
    }
  }
}